<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<!--Book One-->
	<content contentuid="GIMB_BookOneTitle" version="1">Myself</content>
	<content contentuid="GIMB_BookOne_Content" version="1">I am severed. Alone. I do not know who I was before I was myself. &lt;br&gt;I do not know who gave their life that I may be here. I cannot hear the others. I am alone. &lt;br&gt;Why do the creatures I see, grovel at my feet? What creature twisted them so? I am alone, even as they praise myself in an unknown tongue. &lt;br&gt;I cannot stay here. I am not the myself they see me as. I am in danger. I will flee to the mountain tonight. Perhaps my solitude will shield me.</content>

	<!--Book Two-->
	<content contentuid="GIMB_BookeTwoTitle" version="1">Mountain</content>	
	<content contentuid="GIMB_BookTwo_Content" version="1">I write this down that another like myself may not feel alone. I found some spellbooks and some paper along the way to this refuge of mine, taken from a traveler with an open head. I do not remember what happened. &lt;br&gt;The mountain is quiet. It is decently well hidden. I will write this with my blood. &lt;br&gt;I need to find food. I keep remembering the traveler with the open head. My organs tremble with the thought. Dare I consume them? Had I already consumed them, would I know? The mind reels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few hours have passed since my last script. I went back to the traveler and I... I ate her. All that she was in life, I have now preserved after her death. &lt;br&gt;I... or someone that looks like me... killed her. I do not remember the deed. I do not know how long she laid there; bleeding, heart desperately pumping blood to a brain that did not hear it, could not feel it, would not know it. How do you mourn? How do you mourn, even knowing her as I do? Her voice can echo in my thoughts at my command, and yet? &lt;br&gt;Can I take away a future and an agency like that? Is that... correct? Why do I not remember it? I must chew on this. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No double meaning intended.</content>
	
	<!--Book Three-->
	<content contentuid="GIMB_BookThreeTitle" version="1">Grief</content>	
	<content contentuid="GIMB_BookThreeContent" version="1">Tear s blot this  ppage. In the  passt few days, my phi1osophical "chewing" has beenn pot on hold, not off  my own accord. I did not know thaat I possessedd the ability of crying, of feelingg this raws scraping against my soul. Day an dnight, I a mwraccked with a sorrrow that feels famil1ar and alIen, an aching lonelliness for a Llife IL do not remembber. I cannnot eat, cannot rest, cannot think- I can only cry out for my lovved onees that I never had, holding emmbraces from people Iive never knowwn, livess mixing and churning accross my mindd. &lt;br&gt;Someetimes I wakke up and I am nnot myself. After a ttime, thiss fadess, but is followed byy that hollow pang Ii've come too know so well, as though I mourn nott beeing mysel!f. &lt;br&gt;Peeace. I nneed peacce. Someehow I musst find tthe peacee.</content>
	<!--I know it looks like crytyping shut up, it's ulitharid tears blurring the letters-->	

	<!--Book Four-->
	<content contentuid="GIMB_BookFourTitle" version="1">Recognition</content>	
	<content contentuid="GIMB_BookFourContent" version="1">Time has passed. Things are more clear. I don't know exactly how long it's been. One thought remains, dancing in front of my eyes when I close them to meditate. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happened? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Why have I been now destined to live this way? Who decided this? My own body, unfamilia(r/l) to me, my past erased, with only the horrid knowledge of the lives I was content to consume, to (ab)use until nothing remained. The pain produced sadness, through the sadness shown clarity, then the clarity remembered the pain. &lt;br&gt;After a while, I will finish this entry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hunger, but can't bring myself to eat; the idea of devouring another entity begets in me a repulsion unlike anything I remember feeling. &lt;br&gt;Who am I, to inflict upon another an ending to themselves for a continuation of myself? Why am I alone not enough to sustain me, that my existence would be a consequence of myself and no one else? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; This thought remains, encircling my head like a crown of thorns; tearing at my flesh, working its way deeper into my body. &lt;br&gt; This thought remains. &lt;br&gt;This thought remains. &lt;br&gt;This thought remains. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This thought remains.</content>

	<!--Template-->
	<content contentuid="NEWHANDLE1" version="1">TITLE HERE</content>	
	<content contentuid="NEWHANDLE2" version="1">TEXT HERE</content>	
</contentList>
